nikkipeel.com npeel3497@gmail.com

Nikki Peel

SKILLS

I'm a Junior Web Developer with over 10 years of Customer Service experience. I've completed courses in Web Development offered by Udemy, Codecademy, Udacity, Sololearn, FreeCodeCamp, and more. I'm currently enrolled in Udemy's Advanced Web Developer, Advanced CSS/Sass, Advanced Javascript, and Wordpress Development Bootcamps. I'm very familiar with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and Javascript (including React, Express, Node, and jQuery). Most of my current projects can be found on my CodePen profile that I update regularly.

Though my education is geared toward Full Stack and Front-End Web Development, I still maintain an enthusiastic, problem-solving mindset that has always been crucial to Customer Satisfaction. I'm familiar with using the following tools for Support: Zoom, Slack, FreshDesk, Aircall, Microsoft, and Google Suite. I also utilize proper grammar and etiquette when drafting emails at over 80wpm.

EXPERIENCE

Collage.com, Michigan - Customer Satisfaction Representative

Oct 2019 - Dec 2019

- Providing live online support to Collage Customers
- Using Freshdesk, Freshchat, Google Suite, and Aircall for support
- Finding and applying solutions to account or order problems

Freelance, Michigan - Web Developer

Feb 2017 - PRESENT

- Creating dynamic, responsive web sites using HTML, CSS, Javascript, and more
- Creating and maintaining Wordpress sites; including the development of a custom theme

Restaurants (various), Michigan — Server, Line Cook, Manager

Apr 2006 - Apr 2019

- Ensure proper sanitation, food preparation, and equipment maintenance
- Resolve guest concerns in an efficient and courteous manner

- Create and adhere to a structured plan for staff to include assignment of work-stations and development of a food preparation list
- Perform regular office duties such as: manage cash, catalogue data, order product, create schedules, and open/close the store

EDUCATION

Udemy, Online - Various Courses

SEP 2019 - PRESENT, REMOTE

Web Developer, Advanced Web Developer, Advanced CSS/Sass, Advanced Javascript, React, and React Native Web Development Bootcamps

Codecademy, Online - Various Courses

FEB 2017 - SEP 2018, REMOTE

Courses completed as part of the Web Development Path: HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Git, AngularJS, PHP, Python

Baker College, Michigan - Graphic Communications

FEB 2007 - MAR 2009, FLINT

Business, Marketing, Advertising, Communications, and Graphic Design courses completed

LINKS

<u>LinkedIn</u> <u>CodePen</u>

Github Website